let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many digits of the DNIC (Data Network Identification Code) identify the country?",
    answer: "first three",
    options: [
      "first three",
      "first four",
      "first five",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which is true about an anonymous inner class?",
    answer: "It can extend exactly one class or implement exactly one interface.",
    options: [
      "	It can extend exactly one class and implement exactly one interface.",
      "It can extend exactly one class and can implement multiple interfaces.",
      "It can extend exactly one class or implement exactly one interface.",
      "It can implement multiple interfaces regardless of whether it also extends a class."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In a mortar, the binding material is",
    answer: "cement",
    options: [
      "cement",
      "sand",
      "surkhi",
      "cinder"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Wrought iron contains carbon upto",
    answer: "0.25%",
    options: [
      "0.25%",
      "1.0%",
      "1.5%",
      "2%"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Tin based white metals are used, where bearings are subjected to",
    answer: "high pressure & load",
    options: [
      "high pressure & load",
      "low pressure & load.",
      "high temperature.",
      "	large surface wear."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Materials with lots of free electrons are called",
    answer: "conductors",
    options: [
      "filters",
      "semiconductors",
      "	insulators",
      "conductors"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A half-moon protractor is divided into how many degrees",
    answer: "180",
    options: [
      "360",
      "180",
      "270",
      "310"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The friction experienced by a body, when in motion, is known as",
    answer: "dynamic friction",
    options: [
      "rolling friction",
      "dynamic friction",
      "limiting friction",
      "static friction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A zinc diffusion process is called",
    answer: "sherardizing",
    options: [
      "galvanising",
      "anodising",
      "	parkerising",
      "sherardizing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The motion of the cam is transferred to the valves through",
    answer: "rocker arms",
    options: [
      "	pistons",
      "rocker arms",
      "camshaft pulley",
      "valve stems"
    ]
  },
];